Hi.
嗨
This guy says "hello," I wanna kill myself.
这家伙说"嗨"的时候 我却想杀了我自己
Are you okay, sweetie?
你还好吧 亲爱的？
I feel like someone reached my throat,
我就感觉好像某人伸手进我的喉咙
grabbed my small intestine, pulled it out of my mouth...
抓住我的小肠 从我的嘴里拉出来
- ...and tied it around my neck.  - Cookie?
- 再在我的脖子上打结…  - 要吃饼干吗？
Carol moved her stuff out today.
卡萝今天搬走了她的东西
- Let me get you some coffee.  - Thanks.
- 我给你拿杯咖啡  - 谢谢
No. No, don't! Stop cleansing my aura.
不 不要  不要清理我的光环
Just leave my aura alone, okay?
不要管我的光环 好吗？
I'll be fine. All right? Really. I hope she'll be very happy.
我会没事的 好吗？真的 我希望她开心
- No, you don't.  - No, I don't.
- 不 你并不希望  - 是的 我不希望
To hell with her. She left me!
叫她去死 是她离开了我
And you never knew she was a lesbian.
你从来都不知道她是女同性恋
No! Okay?
不知道 行了吧
Why does everyone keep fixating on that?
为什么每个人老是要提出来？
She didn't know. How should I know?
她都不知道 我又怎么会知道？
Sometimes I wish I was a lesbian.
有时候我希望我是女同性恋…
Did I say that out loud?
我讲得很大声吗？
All right, Ross. Look, you're feeling a lot of pain right now.
没事的 罗斯 你现在感到很痛苦
You're angry. You're hurting.
你很生气 很伤心
Can I tell you what the answer is?
我能告诉你解决方法是什么吗？
Strip joints!
脱衣舞厅
Come on, you're single. Have some hormones.
别这样 你单身了 有需求的
See, but I don't want to be single, okay?
我不想单身 好吗？
I just wanna be married again.
我只想…再次结婚